i2list.com 2013-11-21

# i2List.com Free Classifieds Site

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Welcome to i2List.com. 

By using the services available from www.i2list.com (the “Site”) you are agreeing to the following terms and conditions (the “Agreement”) with i2List, LLC. regarding data (“Content”) posted to the Site. Answers to your questions can be found at the Q&A section of the Site. You must read and accept all terms and conditions in this User Agreement and Privacy Policy before using i2list.com. This agreement is effective April 6th, 2010 for all current users. It becomes effective upon acceptance for new users of the Site. 

i2list.com are respectful of your privacy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. For your own information and protection, please read the following policy that protects the i2list.com web site and all matters posted on or appearing on the web site i2list.com and check back from time to time for changes to the policy. By visiting and using i2list.com, you agree that your use of i2list.com, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our User Agreement. Because the Internet is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy in the future, in which case we will post the changes to this Privacy Policy on i2list.com and update the effective date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use i2list.com after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. 

Protection of users’ privacy is a very important principle. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. The information you provide to us is stored on computers located in the United States that are protected by physical and technological security means. 

Your use of the i2list.com website signifies acknowledgement of and agreement to our Privacy Policy. You further acknowledge and agree that i2list.com may, at its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, as well as your information, such as email addresses, IP addresses, timestamps, and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal process; enforce the Agreement; respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to claims that contact information (e.g. phone number, street address) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; protect the rights, property, or personal safety of i2list.com, its users or the general public. 

Use of Data. 

We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites. 

Collection of data. 

You are not required to provide any information if you do not want to. Please be aware that the e-mail address you provide and any other information you enter may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally (depending on choices you make during the ad or event posting process, or depending on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). 

Cookies. 

To help make our sites more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we may utilize a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of computer code that is deposited on your hard drive by our site. Browsers typically recognize when a cookie has been sent to your computer and give you the option to refuse or allow it. A cookie does not actually identify you, just the computer that you are using to access our site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers, content partners and sites that are reached from links on our site may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we cannot control. 

We use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs so we can deliver a better and more personalized service. It is a cookie, for example, that allows us to deliver to you any personalized information each time you visit a site. 

NO GUARANTEES. 

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data. 

Contact Information. 

If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact customer service at directory@i2list.com 

Changes to this Agreement. 

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditions at any time. Such modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof. We ask that you review this agreement on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes. 

Created by, 

**i2List Team**
